Dick Clark Papers
Dick Clark Papers
- Scripts
  - Rock, Roll and Remember
    - Show #164, Mar 30-31, 1985; Little Anthony & the Imperials (Box 32)
    - Show #165, Apr 6-7, 1985; Steve Miller (Box 32)
    - Show #166, Apr 13-14, 1985; Doors (Box 32)
    - Show #167, Apr 20-21, 1985; Miracles (Box 32)
    - Show #168, Apr 27-28, 1985; Eagles (Box 33)
    - Show #169, May 4-5, 1985; Mamas & the Papas (Box 33)
    - Show #170, May 11-12, 1985; Doobie Brothers (Box 33)
    - Show #171, May 18-19, 1985; Moody Blues (Box 33)
    - Show #172, May 25-26, 1985; Hall & Oates (Box 33)
    - Show #173, Jun 1-2, 1985; Monkees (Box 33)
    - Show #174, Jun 8-9, 1985; Helen Reddy (Box 33)
    - Show #175, Jun 15-16, 1985; ABBA (Box 33)
    - Show #176, Jun 22-23, 1985; Al Green (Box 34)
    - Show #177, Jun 29-30, 1985; Johnny Mathis (Box 34)
    - Show #178, Jul 6-7, 1985; Ricky Nelson (Box 34)
    - Show #179, Jul 13-14, 1985; Gary Lewis & the Playboys (Box 34)
    - Show #180, Jul 20-21, 1985; Kinks (Box 34)
    - Show #181, Jul 27-28, 1985; Jerry Butler (Box 34)
    - Show #182, Aug 3-4, 1985; Searchers (Box 34)
    - Show #183, Aug 10-11, 1985; Tommy Roe (Box 34)
    - Show #184, Aug 17-18, 1985; Rascals (Box 35)
    - Show #185, Aug 24-25, 1985; Kool & the Gang (Box 35)
    - Show #186, Aug 31-Sep 1, 1985; Stevie Wonder (Box 35)
    - Show #187, Sep 7-8, 1985; Kenny Loggins (Box 35)
    - Show #188, Sep 14-15, 1985; Lovin’ Spoonful (Box 35)
    - Show #189, Sep 21-22, 1985; Who (Box 35)
    - Show #190, Sep 28-29, 1985; Hollies (Box 35)
    - Show #191, Oct 5-6, 1985; Four Tops (Box 35)
    - Show #192, Oct 12-13, 1985; Barry Manilow (Box 36)
    - Show #193, Oct 19-20, 1985; Guess Who (Box 36)
    - Show #194, Oct 26-27, 1985; Simon & Garfunkel (Box 36)
    - Show #195, Nov 2-3, 1985; Turtles (Box 36)
    - Show #196, Nov 9-10, 1985; Sonny & Cher (Box 36)
    - Show #197, Nov 16-17, 1985; Olivia Newton-John (Box 36)
    - Show #198, Nov 23-24, 1985; Billy Joel (Box 36)
    - Show #199, Nov 30-Dec 1, 1985; John Denver (Box 36)
    - Show #200, Dec 7-8, 1985; Diana Ross (Box 36)
    - Show #201, Dec 14-15, 1985; George Harrison (Box 37)
    - Show #202, Dec 21-22, 1985; RRR Christmas Show (Box 37)
    - Show #203, Dec 28-29, 1985; Linda Ronstadt (Box 37)
    - Show #204, Jan 4-5, 1986; Bobby Vee (Box 37)
    - Show #205, Jan 11-12, 1986; Jay & the Americans (Box 37)
    - Show #206, Jan 18-19, 1986; Roberta Flack (Box 37)
    - Show #207, Jan 25-26, 1986; Jackson Five (Box 37)
    - Show #208, Feb 1-2, 1986; Brenda Lee (Box 37)
    - Show #209, Feb 8-9, 1986; Carpenters (Box 37)
    - Show #210, Feb 15-16, 1986; Temptations (Box 37)
    - Show #211, Feb 22-23, 1986; Crosby, Stills, & Nash (Box 38)
    - Show #212, Mar 1-2, 1986; Neil Diamond (Box 38)
    - Show #213, Mar 8-9, 1986; Fleetwood Mac (Box 38)
    - Show #214, Mar 15-16, 1986; Jackie Wilson (Box 38)
    - Show #215, Mar 22-23, 1986; Herb Alpert & the Tijuana Brass (Box 38)
    - Show #216, Mar 29-30, 1986; Herman’s Hermits (Box 38)
    - Show #217, Apr 5-6, 1986; Anne Murray (Box 38)
    - Show #218, Apr 12-13, 1986; Sly & the Family Stone (Box 38)
    - Show #219, Apr 19-20, 1986; Mary Wells (Box 38)
    - Show #220, Apr 26-27, 1986; Elton John (Box 38)
    - Show #221, May 3-4, 1986; Creedence Clearwater Revival (Box 39)
    - Show #222, May 10-11, 1986; Martha & the Vandellas (Box 39)
    - Show #223, May 17-18, 1986; Bobby Rydell (Box 39)
    - Show #224, May 24-25, 1986; Supremes (Box 39)
    - Show #225, May 31-Jun 1, 1986; Beach Boys (Box 39)
    - Show #226, Jun 7-8, 1986; Roy Orbison (Box 39)
    - Show #227, Jun 14-15, 1986; Al Green (Box 39)
    - Show #228, Jun 21-22, 1986; Dionne Warwick (Box 39)
    - Show #229, Jun 28-29, 1986; Monkees (Box 39)
    - Show #230, Jul 5-6, 1986; Chicago (Box 39)
    - Show #231, Jul 12-13, 1986; Doors (Box 40)
    - Show #232, Jul 19-20, 1986; Hollies (Box 40)
    - Show #233, Jul 26-27, 1986; Gladys Knight & the Pips (Box 40)
    - Show #234, Aug 2-3, 1986; Commodores (Box 40)
    - Show #235, Aug 9-10, 1986; Captain & Tennille (Box 40)
    - Show #236, Aug 16-17, 1986; Dion (Box 40)
    - Show #237, Aug 23-24, 1986; O’Jays (Box 40)
    - Show #238, Aug 30-31, 1986; Jan & Dean (Box 40)
    - Show #239, Sep 6-7, 1986; Association (Box 40)
    - Show #240, Sep 13-14, 1986; Tom Jones (Box 41)
    - Show #241, Sep 20-21, 1986; The Who (Box 41)
    - Show #242, Sep 27-28, 1986; Moody Blues (Box 41)
    - Show #243, Oct 4-5, 1986; Stylistics (Box 41)
    - Show #244, Oct 11-12, 1986; Pointer Sisters (Box 41)
    - Show #245, Oct 18-19, 1986; Paul McCartney (Box 41)
    - Show #246, Oct 25-26, 1986; Miracles (Box 41)
    - Show #247, Nov 1-2, 1986; Kool & the Gang (Box 41)
    - Show #248, Nov 8-9, 1986; Paul Revere & the Raiders (Box 41)
    - Show #249, Nov 15-16, 1986; Seals & Crofts (Box 41)
    - Show #250, Nov 22-23, 1986; Carly Simon (Box 42)
    - Show #251, Nov 29-30, 1986; Rod Stewart (Box 42)
    - Show #252, Dec 6-7, 1986; Dave Clark Five (Box 42)
    - Show #253, Dec 13-14, 1986; Tony Orlando & Dawn (Box 42)
    - Show #254, Dec 20-21, 1986; RRR Christmas Show (Box 42)
    - Show #255, Dec 27-28, 1986; Bee Gees (Box 42)
    - Show #256, Jan 3-4, 1987; Righteous Brothers (Box 42)
    - Show #257, Jan 10-11, 1987; Johnny Rivers (Box 42)
    - Show #258, Jan 17-18, 1987; Earth, Wind & Fire (Box 42)
    - Show #259, Jan 24-25, 1987; Electric Light Orchestra (Box 42)
    - Show #260, Jan 31-Feb 1, 1987; Four Tops (Box 43)
    - Show #261, Feb 7-8, 1987; Johnny Mathis (Box 43)
    - Show #262, Feb 14-15, 1987; Drifters (Box 43)
    - Show #263, Feb 21-22, 1987; Rick Nelson (Box 43)
    - Show #264, Feb 28-Mar 1, 1987; Fifth Dimension (Box 43)
    - Show #265, Mar 7-8, 1987; B J Thomas (Box 43)
    - Show #266, Mar 14-15, 1987; Turtles (Box 43)
    - Show #267, Mar 21-22, 1987; John Denver (Box 43)
    - Show #268, Mar 28-29, 1987; Sonny & Cher (Box 43)
    - Show #269, Apr 4-5, 1987; Grass Roots (Box 44)
    - Show #270, Apr 11-12, 1987; Ray Charles (Box 44)
    - Show #271, Apr 18-19, 1987; Four Seasons (Box 44)
    - Show #272, Apr 25-26, 1987; Fleetwood Mac (Box 44)
    - Show #273, May 2-3, 1987; Animals (Box 44)
    - Show #274, May 9-10, 1987; Doobie Brothers (Box 44)
    - Show #275, May 16-17, 1987; Bobby Darin (Box 44)
    - Show #276, May 23-24, 1987; Bread (Box 44)
    - Show #277, May 30-31, 1987; Beach Boys (Box 44)
    - Show #278, Jun 6-7, 1987; Spinners (Box 45)
    - Show #279, Jun 13-14, 1987; Jay & the Americans (Box 45)
    - Show #280, Jun 20-21, 1987; Lovin’ Spoonful (Box 45)
    - Show #281, Jun 27-28, 1987; Stevie Wonder (Box 45)
    - Show #282, Jul 4-5, 1987; Gary Lewis & the Playboys (Box 45)
    - Show #283, Jul 11-12, 1987; Three Dog Night (Box 45)
    - Show #284, Jul 18-19, 1987; Jefferson Airplane (Box 45)
    - Show #285, Jul 25-26, 1987; Temptations (Box 45)
    - Show #286, Aug 1-2, 1987; Roy Orbison (Box 46)
    - Show #287, Aug 8-9, 1987; Rascals (Box 46)
    - Show #288, Aug 15-16, 1987; Simon & Garfunkel (Box 46)
    - Show #289, Aug 22-23, 1987; Searchers; cue sheets only (Box 46)
    - Show #290, Aug 29-30, 1987; Linda Ronstadt (Box 46)
    - Show #291, Sep 5-6, 1987; Buddy Holly (Box 46)
    - Show #292, Sep 12-13, 1987; Dion & the Belmonts (Box 46)
    - Show #293, Sep 19-20, 1987; Elton John (Box 46)
    - Show #294, Sep 26-27, 1987; Del Shannon (Box 46)
    - Show #295, Oct 3-4, 1987; Dan Fogelberg (Box 46)
    - Show #296, Oct 10-11, 1987; Kenny Loggins (Box 46)
    - Show #297, Oct 17-18, 1987; Jackson Five (Box 46)
    - Show #298, Oct 24-25, 1987; Duane Eddy (Box 46)
    - Show #299, Oct 31-Nov 1, 1987; Shirelles (Box 46)
    - Show #300, Nov 7-8, 1987; Donovan (Box 47)
    - Show #301, Nov 14-15, 1987; Bob Seger (Box 47)
    - Show #302, Nov 21-22, 1987; Kinks (Box 47)
    - Show #303, Nov 28-29, 1987; Little River Band (Box 47)
    - Show #304, Dec 5-6, 1987; Peter & Gordon (Box 47)
    - Show #305, Dec 12-13, 1987; Jerry Butler (Box 47)
    - Show #306, Dec 19-20, 1987; RRR Christmas Show (Box 47)
    - Show #307, Dec 26-27, 1987; Billy Joel (Box 47)
    - Show #308, Jan 2-3, 1988; Supremes (Box 47)
    - Show #309, Jan 9-10, 1988; Everly Brothers (Box 47)
    - Show #310, Jan 16-17, 1988; America (Box 47)
    - Show #311, Jan 23-24, 1988; Mamas & the Papas (Box 47)
    - Show #312, Jan 30-31, 1988; Platters (Box 47)
    - Show #313, Feb 6-7, 1988; Creedence Clearwater Revival (Box 47)
    - Show #314, Feb 13-14, 1988; Love Songs Special (Box 47)
    - Show #315, Feb 20-21, 1988; Bobby Vee (Box 48)
    - Show #316, Feb 27-28, 1988; Martha & the Vandellas (Box 48)
    - Show #317, Mar 5-6, 1988; Anne Murray (Box 48)
    - Show #318, Mar 12-13, 1988; Neil Diamond (Box 48)
    - Show #319, Mar 19-20, 1988; Association (Box 48)
    - Show #320, Mar 26-27, 1988; Guess Who (Box 48)
    - Show #321, Apr 2-3, 1988; Brook Benton (Box 48)
    - Show #322, Apr 9-10, 1988; Peter, Paul & Mary (Box 48)
    - Show #323, Apr 16-17, 1988; Sly & the Family Stone (Box 48)
    - Show #324, Apr 23-24, 1988; Paul Anka (Box 48)
    - Show #325, Apr 30-May 1, 1988; Crosby, Stills & Nash (Box 48)
    - Show #326, May 7-8, 1988; Herman’s Hermits (Box 48)
    - Show #327, May 14-15, 1988; Carpenters (Box 48)
    - Show #328, May 21-22, 1988; Little Richard (Box 48)
    - Show #329, May 28-29, 1988; Neil Sedaka (Box 48)
    - Show #330 [not in collection], Jun 4-5, 1988; Tommy Roe
    - Show #331, Jun 11-12, 1988; Pat Boone (Box 48)
    - Show #332, Jun 18-19, 1988; Dusty Springfield (Box 49)
    - Show #333, Jun 25-26, 1988; Beatles (Box 49)
    - Show #334, Jul 2-3, 1988; Jan & Dean (Box 49)
    - Show #335, Jul 9-10, 1988; ABBA (Box 49)
    - Show #336, Jul 16-17, 1988; Lesley Gore (Box 49)
    - Show #337, Jul 23-24, 1988; Gene Pitney (Box 49)
    - Show #338, Jul 30-31, 1988; James Taylor (Box 49)
    - Show #339, Aug 6-7, 1988; Glen Campbell (Box 49)
    - Show #340, Aug 13-14, 1988; Gladys Knight & the Pips (Box 49)
    - Show #341, Aug 20-21, 1988; Johnny Rivers (Box 49)
    - Show #342, Aug 27-28, 1988; Paul Revere & the Raiders (Box 49)
    - Show #343, Sep 3-4, 1988; Righteous Brothers (Box 49)
    - Show #344, Sep 10-11, 1988; Al Green (Box 49)
    - Show #345, Sep 17-18, 1988; Beach Boys (Box 49)
    - Show #346, Sep 24-25, 1988; Jackie Wilson (Box 49)
    - Show #347, Oct 1-2, 1988; Four Seasons (Box 50)
    - Show #348, Oct 8-9, 1988; John Lennon (Box 50)
    - Show #349, Oct 15-16, 1988; Chicago (Box 50)
    - Show #350, Oct 22-23, 1988; Miracles (Box 50)
    - Show #351, Oct 29-30, 1988; Do Wop Special (Box 50)
    - Show #352, Nov 5-6, 1988; Chuck Berry (Box 50)
    - Show #353, Nov 12-13, 1988; Four Tops (Box 50)
    - Show #354, Nov 19-20, 1988; Tommy James & the Shondells (Box 50)
    - Show #355, Nov 26-27, 1988; Stevie Wonder (Box 50)
    - Show #356, Dec 3-4, 1988; Earth, Wind & Fire (Box 50)
    - Show #357, Dec 10-11, 1988; Rascals (Box 50)
    - Show #358, Dec 17-18, 1988; Temptations (Box 50)
    - Show #359, Dec 24-25, 1988; RRR Christmas Show (Box 50)
    - Show #360, Dec 31-Jan 1, 1989; Bee Gees (Box 50)
    - Show #361, Jan 7-8, 1989; Three Dog Night (Box 50)
    - Show #362, Jan 14-15, 1989; B J Thomas (Box 50)
    - Show #363, Jan 21-22, 1989; Dion & the Belmonts (Box 50)
    - Show #364, Jan 28-29, 1989; Drifters (Box 50)
    - Show #365, Feb 4-5, 1989; Del Shannon (Box 51)
    - Show #366, Feb 11-12, 1989; Doobie Brothers (Box 51)
    - Show #367, Feb 18-19, 1989; Girl Groups (Box 51)
    - Show #368, Feb 25-26, 1989; Ray Charles (Box 51)
    - Show #369, Mar 4-5, 1989; Johnny Mathis (Box 51)
    - Show #370, Mar 11-12, 1989; Roy Orbison (Box 51)
    - Show #371, Mar 18-19, 1989; Mary Wells (Box 51)
    - Show #372, Mar 25-26, 1989; Elton John (Box 51)
    - Show #373, Apr 1-2, 1989; Rick Nelson (Box 51)
    - Show #374, Apr 8-9, 1989; Jr Walker (Box 51)
    - Show #375, Apr 15-16, 1989; Tom Jones (Box 51)
    - Show #376, Apr 22-23, 1989; Jay & the Americans (Box 51)
    - Show #377, Apr 29-30, 1989; Seals & Crofts (Box 51)
    - Show #378, May 6-7, 1989; Carly Simon (Box 51)
    - Show #379, May 13-14, 1989; George Harrison (Box 51)
    - Show #380, May 20-21, 1989; Everly Brothers (Box 51)
    - Show #381, May 27-28, 1989; Supremes (Box 52)
    - Show #382, Jun 3-4, 1989; Spinners (Box 52)
    - Show #383, Jun 10-11, 1989; Dave Clark Five (Box 52)
    - Show #384, Jun 17-18, 1989; Little Richard (Box 52)
    - Show #385, Jun 24-25, 1989; Marvin Gaye (Box 52)
    - Show #386, Jul 1-2, 1989; Jan & Dean (Box 52)
    - Show #387, Jul 8-9, 1989; Guess Who (Box 52)
    - Show #388, Jul 15-16, 1989; Hollies (Box 52)
    - Show #389, Jul 22-23, 1989; Connie Francis (Box 52)
    - Show #390, Jul 29-30, 1989; Ringo Starr (Box 52)
    - Show #391, Aug 5-6, 1989; Four Seasons (Box 52)
    - Show #392, Aug 12-13, 1989; Martha & the Vandellas (Box 52)
    - Show #393, Aug 19-20, 1989; Petula Clark (Box 52)
    - Show #394, Aug 26-27, 1989; James Taylor (Box 52)
    - Show #395, Sep 2-3, 1989; Buddy Holly (Box 52)
    - Show #396, Sep 9-10, 1989; Chubby Checker (Box 52)
    - Show #397, Sep 16-17, 1989; John Denver (Box 53)
    - Show #398, Sep 23-24, 1989; Fleetwood Mac (Box 53)
    - Show #399, Sep 30-Oct 1, 1989; Lovin’ Spoonful (Box 53)
    - Show #400, Oct 7-8, 1989; O’Jays (Box 53)
    - Show #401, Oct 14-15, 1989; Anne Murray (Box 53)
    - Show #402, Oct 21-22, 1989; Stylistics (Box 53)
    - Show #403, Oct 28-29, 1989; Bobby Rydell (Box 53)
    - Show #404, Nov 4-5, 1989; Fifth Dimension (Box 53)
    - Show #405, Nov 11-12, 1989; Carole King (Box 53)
    - Show #406, Nov 18-19, 1989; Creedence Clearwater Revival (Box 53)
    - Show #407, Nov 25-26, 1989; Simon & Garfunkel (Box 53)
    - Show #408, Dec 2-3, 1989; Gladys Knight & the Pips (Box 53)
    - Show #409, Dec 9-10, 1989; Gary Lewis & the Playboys (Box 53)
    - Show #410, Dec 16-17, 1989; Bobby Darin (Box 53)
    - Show #411, Dec 23-24, 1989; RRR Christmas Show (Box 53)
    - Show #412, Dec 30-31, 1989; Miracles (Box 54)
    - Show #413, Jan 6-7, 1990; Hollies (Box 54)
    - Show #414, Jan 13-14, 1990; Temptations (Box 54)
    - Show #415, Jan 20-21, 1990; Herman’s Hermits (Box 54)
    - Show #416, Jan 27-28, 1990; Bobby Vee (Box 54)
    - Show #417, Feb 3-4, 1990; Beatles (Box 54)
    - Show #418, Feb 10-11, 1990; Bobby Vinton (Box 54)
    - Show #419, Feb 17-18, 1990; Tommy James & the Shondells (Box 54)
    - Show #420, Feb 24-25, 1990; Johnny Rivers (Box 54)
    - Show #421, Mar 3-4, 1990; Four Seasons (Box 54)
    - Show #422, Mar 10-11, 1990; Stevie Wonder (Box 54)
    - Show #423, Mar 17-18, 1990; Three Dog Night (Box 54)
    - Show #424, Mar 24-25, 1990; Elvis Presley (Box 54)
    - Show #425, Mar 31-Apr 1, 1990; Petula Clark (Box 54)
    - Show #426, Apr 7-8, 1990; John Lennon (Box 54)
    - Show #427, Apr 14-15, 1990; Supremes (Box 54)
    - Show #428, Apr 21-22, 1990; Roy Orbison (Box 55)
    - Show #429, Apr 28-29, 1990; Neil Sedaka (Box 55)
    - Show #430, May 5-6, 1990; Monkees (Box 55)
    - Show #431, May 12-13, 1990; Lesley Gore (Box 55)
    - Show #432, May 19-20, 1990; Buddy Holly (Box 55)
    - Show #433, May 26-27, 1990; Elton John (Box 55)
    - Show #434, Jun 2-3, 1990; Beach Boys (Box 55)
    - Show #435, Jun 9-10, 1990; Marvin Gaye (Box 55)
    - Show #436-475 [not in collection], 1990 Jun - 1991 Mar
    - Show #476-520, Mar 1991-Jan 1992; cue sheets only; 3 folders (Box 55)
    - Show #92-05/521, Feb 1-2, 1992; Buddy Holly (Box 55)
    - Show #92-06/522, Feb 8-9, 1992; Tommy James & the Shondells (Box 55)
    - Show #92-07/523, Feb 15-16, 1992; Martha & the Vandellas (Box 55)
    - Show #92-08/524, Feb 22-23, 1992; George Harrison (Box 56)
    - Show #92-09/525, Feb 29-Mar 1, 1992; Herman’s Hermits (Box 56)
    - Show #92-10/526, Mar 7-8, 1992; Neil Sedaka (Box 56)
    - Show #92-11/527, Mar 14-15, 1992; Supremes (Box 56)
    - Show #92-12/528, Mar 21-22, 1992; Elton John (Box 56)
    - Show #92-13/529, Mar 28-29, 1992; Marvin Gaye (Box 56)
    - Show #92-14/530, Apr 4-5, 1992; Three Dog Night (Box 56)
    - Show #92-15/531, Apr 11-12, 1992; Simon & Garfunkel (Box 56)
    - Show #92-16/532, Apr 18-19, 1992; Bobby Vee (Box 56)
    - Show #92-17/533, Apr 25-26, 1992; Neil Diamond (Box 56)
    - Show #92-18/534, May 2-3, 1992; Four Seasons (Box 56)
    - Show #92-19/535, May 9-10, 1992; Stevie Wonder (Box 56)
    - Show #92-20/536, May 16-17, 1992; Cher (Box 56)
    - Show #92-21/537, May 23-24, 1992; Monkees (Box 56)
    - Show #92-22/538, May 30-31, 1992; Bee Gees (Box 57)
    - Show #92-23/539, Jun 6-7, 1992; Ringo Starr (Box 57)
    - Show #92-24/540, Jun 13-14, 1992; Dion (Box 57)
    - Show #92-25/541, Jun 20-21, 1992; Lesley Gore (Box 57)
    - Show #92-26/542, Jun 27-28, 1992; Beach Boys (Box 57)
    - Show #92-27/543, Jul 4-5, 1992; Four Tops (Box 57)
    - Show #92-28/544, Jul 11-12, 1992; Everly Brothers (Box 57)
    - Show #92-29/545, Jul 18-19, 1992; Paul McCartney (Box 57)
    - Show #92-30/546, Jul 25-26, 1992; Gary Lewis & the Playboys (Box 57)
    - Show #92-31/547, Aug 1-2, 1992; Miracles (Box 57)
    - Show #92-32/548, Aug 8-9, 1992; Creedence Clearwater Revival (Box 57)
    - Show #92-33/549, Aug 15-16, 1992; Elvis Presley (Box 57)
    - Show #92-34/550, Aug 22-23, 1992; Gene Pitney (Box 57)
    - Show #92-35/551, Aug 29-30, 1992; Lovin’ Spoonful (Box 57)
    - Show #92-36/552, Sep 5-6, 1992; Jan & Dean (Box 58)
    - Show #92-37/553, Sep 12-13, 1992; Mamas & the Papas (Box 58)
    - Show #92-38/554, Sep 19-20, 1992; Ben E. King (Box 58)
    - Show #92-39/555, Sep 26-27, 1992; Bobby Darin (Box 58)
    - Show #92-40/556, Oct -3-4, 1992; Beatles (Box 58)
    - Show #92-41/557, Oct 10-11, 1992; Ray Charles (Box 58)
    - Show #92-42/558, Oct 17-18, 1992; Fifth Dimension (Box 58)
    - Show #92-43/559, Oct 24-25, 1992; Guess Who (Box 58)
    - Show #92-44/560, Oct 31-Nov 1, 1992; Simon & Garfunkel (Box 58)
    - Show #92-45/561, Nov 7-8, 1992; Johnny Rivers (Box 58)
    - Show #92-46/562, Nov 14-15, 1992; Petula Clark (Box 58)
    - Show #92-47/563, Nov 21-22, 1992; Temptations (Box 58)
    - Show #92-48/564, Nov 28-29, 1992; Rascals (Box 58)
    - Show #92-49/565, Dec 5-6, 1992; John Lennon (Box 59)
    - Show #92-50/566, Dec 12-13, 1992; Dave Clark Five (Box 59)
    - Show #92-51/567, Dec 19-20, 1992; RRR Christmas Show (Box 59)
    - Show #92-52/568, Dec 26-27, 1992; Rick Nelson (Box 59)
    - Show #93-01/569, Jan 2-3, 1993; Elvis Presley (Box 59)
    - Show #93-02/570, Jan 9-10, 1993; Hollies (Box 59)
    - Show #93-03/571, Jan 16-17, 1993; Roy Orbison (Box 59)
    - Show #93-04/572, Jan 23-24, 1993; Tommy James & the Shondells (Box 59)
    - Show #93-05/573, Jan 30-31, 1993; Buddy Holly (Box 59)
    - Show #93-06/574, Feb 6-7, 1993; Martha & the Vandellas (Box 59)
    - Show #93-07/575, Feb 13-14, 1993; Love Song Special (Box 59)
    - Show #93-08/576, Feb 20-21, 1993; George Harrison (Box 59)
    - Show #93-09/577, Feb 27-28, 1993; Neil Sedaka (Box 59)
    - Show #93-10/578, Mar 6-7, 1993; Herman’s Hermits (Box 59)
    - Show #93-11/579, Mar 13-14, 1993; Supremes (Box 60)
    - Show #93-12/580, Mar 20-21, 1993; Elton John (Box 60)
    - Show #93-13/581, Mar 27-28, 1993; Marvin Gaye (Box 60)
    - Show #93-14/582, Apr 3-4, 1993; Three Dog Night (Box 60)
    - Show #93-15/583, Apr 10-11, 1993; Four Seasons (Box 60)
    - Show #93-16/584, Apr 17-18, 1993; Stevie Wonder (Box 60)
    - Show #93-17/585, Apr 24-25, 1993; Salute to Girl Groups (Box 60)
    - Show #93-18/586, May 1-2, 1993; Dion (Box 60)
    - Show #93-19/587, May 8-9, 1993; Four Tops (Box 60)
    - Show #93-20/588, May 15-16, 1993; Everly Brothers (Box 60)
    - Show #93-21/589, May 22-23, 1993; Paul McCartney (Box 60)
    - Show #93-22/590, May 29-30, 1993; Beach Boys (Box 60)
    - Show #93-23/591, Jun 5-6, 1993; Gary Lewis & the Playboys (Box 60)
    - Show #93-24/592, Jun 12-13, 1993; Miracles (Box 60)
    - Show #93-25/593, Jun 19-20, 1993; Petula Clark (Box 61)
    - Show #93-26/594, Jun 26-27, 1993; Ray Charles (Box 61)
    - Show #93-27/595, Jul 3-4, 1993; All American Hits (Box 61)
    - Show #93-28/596, Jul 10-11, 1993; Temptations (Box 61)
    - Show #93-29/597, Jul 17-18, 1993; Beatles (Box 61)
    - Show #93-30/598, Jul 24-25, 1993; Jan & Dean (Box 61)
    - Show #93-31/599, Jul 31-Aug 1, 1993; Creedence Clearwater Revival (Box 61)
    - Show #93-32/600, Aug 7-8, 1993; Lovin’ Spoonful (Box 61)
    - Show #93-33/601 to 93-40/609 [not in collection], 1993 Aug-Oct
    - Show #93-41/610, Oct 16-17, 1993; Salute to Phil Spector (Box 61)
    - Show #93-42/611, Oct 23-24, 1993; Chicago (Box 61)
    - Show #93-43/612, Oct 30-31, 1993; Turtles (Box 61)
    - Show #93-44/613, Nov 6-7, 1993; Neil Diamond (Box 61)
    - Show #93-45/614, Nov 13-14, 1993; Monkees (Box 61)
    - Show #93-46/615, Nov 20-21, 1993; Gene Pitney (Box 61)
    - Show #93-47/616, Nov 27-28, 1993; Paul Revere & the Raiders (Box 62)
    - Show #93-48/617, Dec 4-5, 1993; Frankie Valli (Box 62)
    - Show #93-49/618, Dec 11-12, 1993; John Lennon (Box 62)
    - Show #93-50/619, Dec 18-19, 1993; RRR Christmas Show (Box 62)
    - Show #93-51/620, Dec 25-26, 1993; Dave Clark Five (Box 62)
    - Show #94-01/621, Jan 1-2, 1994; Dion (Box 62)
    - Show #94-02/622, Jan 8-9, 1994; Bobby Darinhandwritten note on first page says "Army 545" (Box 62)
    - Show #94-03/623, Jan 15-16, 1994; Hollies (Box 62)
    - Show #94-04/624, Jan 22-23, 1994; Three Dog Night (Box 62)
    - Show #94-05/625, Jan 29-30, 1994; Diana Ross (Box 62)
    - Show #94-06/626, Feb 5-6, 1994; Beatles (Box 62)
    - Show #94-07/627, Feb 12-13, 1994; Love Song Special (Box 62)
    - Show #94-08/628, Feb 19-20, 1994; Temptations (Box 62)
    - Show #94-09/629, Feb 26-27, 1994; Roy Orbison (Box 62)
    - Show #94-10/630, Mar 5-6, 1994; Martha & the Vandellas (Box 63)
    - Show #94-11/631, Mar 12-13, 1994; Jan & Dean (Box 63)
    - Show #94-12/632, Mar 19-20, 1994; Grass Roots (Box 63)
    - Show #94-13/633, Mar 26-27, 1994; Gladys Knight & the Pips (Box 63)
    - Show #94-14/634, Apr 2-3, 1994; Everly Brothers (Box 63)
    - Show #94-15/635, Apr 9-10, 1994; Marvin Gaye (Box 63)
    - Show #94-16/636, Apr 16-17, 1994; Rascals (Box 63)
    - Show #94-17/637, Apr 23-24, 1994; Neil Sedaka (Box 63)
    - Show #94-18/638, Apr 30-May 1, 1994; Ray Charles (Box 63)
    - Show #94-19/639, May 7-8, 1994; Four Tops (Box 63)
    - Show #94-20/640, May 14-15, 1994; Elton John (Box 63)
    - Show #94-21/641, May 21-22, 1994; Gary Lewis & the Playboys (Box 63)
    - Show #94-22/642, May 28-29, 1994; Beach Boys (Box 63)
    - Show #94-23/643, Jun 4-5, 1994; Creedence Clearwater Revival (Box 64)
    - Show #94-24/644, Jun 11-12, 1994; Miracles (Box 64)
    - Show #94-25/645, Jun 18-19, 1994; Four Season (Box 64)
    - Show #94-26/646, Jun 25-26, 1994; Petula Clark (Box 64)
    - Show #94-27/647, Jul 2-3, 1994; All American Hits (Box 64)
    - Show #94-28/648, Jul 9-10, 1994; Paul McCartney (Box 64)
    - Show #94-29/649, Jul 16-17, 1994; Supremes (Box 64)
    - Show #94-30/650, Jul 23-24, 1994; Tommy James & the Shondells (Box 64)
    - Show #94-31/651, Jul 30-31, 1994; Drifters (Box 64)
    - Show #94-32/652, Aug 6-7, 1994; Fifth Dimension (Box 64)
    - Show #94-33/653, Aug 13-14, 1994; Elvis (Box 64)
    - Show #94-34/654, Aug 20-21, 1994; Motown Music (Box 64)
    - Show #94-35/655, Aug 27-28, 1994; Guess Who (Box 65)
    - Show #94-36/656, Sep 3-4, 1994; Stevie Wonder (Box 65)
    - Show #94-37/657, Sep 10-11, 1994; Johnny Rivers (Box 65)
    - Show #94-38/658, Sep 17-18, 1994; Phil Spector (Box 65)
    - Show #94-39/659, Sep 24-25, 1994; Chicago (Box 65)
    - Show #94-40/660, Oct 1-2, 1994; Kinks (Box 65)
    - Show #94-41/661, Oct 8-9, 1994; Stylistics (Box 65)
    - Show #94-42/662, Oct 15-16, 1994; Jackie Wilson (Box 65)
    - Show #94-43/663, Oct 22-23, 1994; Simon & Garfunkel (Box 65)